[upbeat music playing]
♪ I'm feeling like... ♪
Heather!
What's up?
-How are you?
-It's been forever!
It's been way too long.
I know. What, like five years?
I think it's been about that. It just
flies by. You look fantastic, as always.
So do you.
[Heather] Brandon and I are old friends.
We did a photoshoot together
back in, like, 2012.
We just clicked on set,
and he's super funny,
and he now works for one of the top
architecture firms in the world.
Wait, so where's this tan from,
because you're in Washington.
[laughs]
Leave it to you to call this out on me.
Seriously, I'm like, I need one, too,
to match you.
Yeah. So, I landed the other day
and I realized I was so pasty white--
Did you go to the beach?
Or did you spray-tan?
You got me, I spray-tanned.
-Typical LA, come on.
-Come on.
I can't believe you just
called me out on that. [chuckles]
I mean, you could've lied.
I can't lie to your face. I look at you.
You know, we're catching up. I just--
-I know.
-Okay, so tell me about you.
I just got back from Slovakia.
I was visiting my boyfriend, Nick.
-Did you speak Slovakian?
-No. I tried to learn a few words.
-I know na zdravie.
-What's that? Like, "Cheers"?
-That's "cheers."
-Okay.
-What does he do?
-Hockey player.
Oh, yeah. And you're in love?
-I am, but it's hard--
-Wait, let me see your hand.
-There's-- I don't see a ring.
-Oh, God. Oh, I don't have a ring.
So you're chasing after him.
-That's a long way to move, and--
-I'm not chasing after him. [chuckles]
It's hard.
-'Cause I'm... I don't--
-Thank you.
Of course, yeah, I love him.
But at the same time,
we've been together two and a half years,
and I don't want to pressure anyone
to marry me ever.
Like, that's not what I want. But...
I don't even know if I want to marry...
We don't know.
-I don't know what I want.
-Okay. So you're back.
Yeah, I'm back. It's stressful
being back in LA,
but I love the opportunity here
and, like, the money here and, like...
Like, where else can I sell
a $20 million home?
Or like, you know, it's insane.
I actually have a potential new listing.
It is around 40 million.
It's not done yet, so it'll be done in,
like, two months, but it's sick.
The views are amazing, the pool,
everything about it.
-If you have this property--
-It would be life changing.
Once I did something like that,
the doors would open completely
for me even more.
There is competition
with some of the girls in my office,
but I'm not worried about it.
-You gotta pull out the nails.
-I'm prepared. For sure.
I mean, I'm not a mean person, though.
I'm not gonna, like--
You're in real estate in LA. [chuckles]
I know. That's my problem.
You're so nice
and you're so attractive in that sense,
and you have to pull out the claws now.
I like being friends with people,
and I feel like it's a natural connection
but I don't wanna, like, lose that
in myself just to make money.
Like, I don't want to. I'd rather have
this connection with someone
and they use me 'cause they trust me,
rather than me, like, hurting people
to, like, get farther in life.
I don't want to be that person.
So, yeah, I might be too nice
and I might not.
But I feel like it's gonna be
my advantage in the end.
If I could bring you
a $40 million client...
I represent some of the largest
manufacturers in China, like billionaires.
You don't have to give me a percentage.
I'll give you a referral, 100 percent.
I have the perfect buyer
who's been looking for a property.
I'm gonna send an email right now,
because--
-Are you being serious?
-I'm being serious.
-Like, we have to make this happen.
-Okay. Make it happen.
-Show me the views, show me the money.
-Show me the money.
-Let's do it.
-Na zdravie!
-La zdravie! Did I say it right?
♪ Hey, you
Tripping off my life ♪
♪ Shivers up and down my spine ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ This is just some crazy, crazy love ♪
♪ My hazy, crazy, crazy, hazy love ♪
Hello, Christine?
-Hi, guys!
-[woman] Hi.
Hi, how are you? Come on in.
Nice to meet you.
So nice to finally meet you. I feel like
I already know you guys, though.
-Christine, thanks for taking the time.
-Come in.
-[Sepi] Thank you.
-[Christine] Look at the view.
[Sepi] Oh, my goodness.
This view's incredible.
This is pretty big.
It's just over 3,000 square feet.
-It's a good size for you.
-It's what we're looking for.
[Sepi] It's bigger than our current home.
But right now, we have a three bedroom,
and I'm pregnant.
So, this one's on the way
and we have a 14 month old.
[Christine] This is four bedroom
and three and a half baths.
[Sepi] Well, we're sold on the view.
-[Christine] A perfect day, too.
-[Max] I love it. I'm sold on the TV.
[Sepi] Is there a yard?
So there is a little area over here.
A California yard.
I would call that a very LA yard.
You still have the patio area,
you know, where they can play.
Let's go take a look at the kitchen.
I think you guys will love it.
This was recently renovated in 2018,
so everything's brand new.
Cappuccino maker.
Come down, make your cappuccino, stare
at yourself in the mirror in the morning.
-This is a really cool vibe.
-Who's gonna clean this?
[Sepi laughs]
I don't know if a mirror behind a stove is
the smartest thing.
-I'm a bit of a cleanness freak.
-He's a clean freak.
Oh, really? So who cleans and who cooks?
-[Max clears throat]
-[Christine laughs]
Both! See how unfair this relationship is?
She's taking really good care of our son.
I gotta give her that credit. Yeah.
[Christine] I'll be honest.
I really don't normally sell to families,
but Max and Sepi are friends with Brett,
and I think Brett was so busy.
It was nice he, you know, connected us.
And families buying houses in the Hills
isn't necessarily as common,
but it's kinda hip and fun
and they're cute and quirky
and I like that about them.
And here's the rooftop.
-[Sepi] Oh, wow.
-What do you guys think of this view?
-[Max] Oh, my God, it's beautiful.
-[Christine] It's incredible.
[Max] This is the place to entertain.
-[Christine] Yep.
-[Sepi] This is wonderful.
-We host a lot.
-This is the perfect spot.
-[Sepi] Having friends over and stuff.
-[Max] There's a barbecue, TV...
I mean, I like it. I like the house a lot,
I think it's beautiful. I think that
if it was just us two, it's a no-brainer.
But maybe, perhaps, if you have
other things that you could show us
that are more conducive to families.
It would be great if there was a yard.
-But stick to the view. I like the view.
-[Christine] Yeah.
I know you love the view.
-[Max] Cool. Thanks.
-[Sepi] Thanks for showing us.
Of course. I'm so glad you guys came.
[Max] Yep.
[Christine] This couple definitely feel
like best friends
and they have
that power-couple element that I love,
and I do want the relationship
that they have. Right now...
not so much. I'm working on my career.
But they made me really like it.
It struck a chord with me.
They're perfect.
♪ This is not a love song ♪
♪ This a not a sing-along ♪
♪ But, ladies, are you with me? ♪
♪ I know that you're with me ♪
♪ Add a little sugar, they say ♪
♪ Be a little sweeter, they say ♪
♪ Gotta give and take ♪
♪ But I say
This time, it's my way ♪
♪ My way, my way ♪
♪ This time, it's my way
My way ♪
♪ This time, it's my way, my way ♪
[woman] Hi!
-How are you?
-I'm good. How are you?
Good. Good to see you.
You, too. Thank you for showing me this.
This is so beautiful.
I love how light and airy and open...
And the vaulted ceilings. It's so pretty.
Yeah, and I know you said,
because we've seen so many,
in some of the other ones,
you mentioned they're just cold.
You know, it's like
they're too contemporary.
You wanted something
a little bit more homey.
Yeah, I feel that with this so much.
[Mary] Finding a home for Emily
has been a little challenging.
She has been looking at all modern homes.
And she said that that's what she wanted,
but I'm starting to notice that
as we're seeing these homes,
she really doesn't like as modern
as she thought she did.
I mean, how great is this?
Just a cute little reading nook.
You know, just chill in the sun.
-I could live here. Right here.
-[chuckles]
[Mary] The house has an amazing flow.
Everything opens up to the outside.
So on a nice day,
just open up all the double doors,
and you have a really nice
indoor-outdoor flow.
All right,
let's get to the master bedroom.
[Emily] Oh, my God, that's so pretty. Wow.
You can even see your pool down below.
[Emily] Oh, I love that.
[Mary] I definitely relate to Emily.
I think we have very similar taste.
I love modern and trendy and cool,
but a little more homey,
kind of like this one.
-I've saved the best for last.
-Wow.
[Mary] The views, obviously, are such
a great selling point on this home.
Yeah. You can actually see all the way
out to the ocean on a clear day.
-Oh, my God, I'm in love with this place.
-[chuckles]
I was hoping you would be.
If you don't buy it,
I would consider buying it.
[Emily] So how much are they asking?
Four-nine-nine-five.
So, just under five million.
-Okay.
-Yeah.
Do you think that they could
come down in price at all?
I think we could probably get it
a little cheaper for you
as long as we come in strong.
I mean, I love it.
But I wanna, like, consult
with my boyfriend first
and kind of see. This is a big move.
This is our first home.
I just wanna make sure
that we're making the right decision.
Of course. Well, think it over
and talk to him, but don't take too long
because I think time is of the essence.
We do need to move on it quickly
if you do want it.
-Okay.
-Yeah, I'll call you.
♪ Turn up the heat ♪
♪ I get it loaded whenever I'm going
Turn up the heat ♪
♪ Turn up the heat ♪
♪ Ready, set, fire... ♪
[Chrishell] Hey.
Well, hi, babe.
Hello, how are you?
-You look amazing. Look at you.
-Thank you.
[Chrishell] Well, you inspired my outfit.
-[Christine] I love it.
-[Chrishell] I thought you would approve.
I am loving this sexy new Chrishell.
-Thanks.
-This is amazing.
I mean, I love you cute and innocent,
but this is a whole other level.
Thank you for inviting me.
I was like, "How would Christine
go through my closet?
"Okay, I got it."
Christine definitely
approves this message.
What are you drinking?
I'll just do, like, a Sauv Blanc.
-Sauv Blanc.
-Thanks.
-Start you out with a water as well?
-No, two shots, no water.
But I have to wake up so early for--
You'll be fine, I promise.
This is one of our signature cocktails
turned into a shot.
It's called the La Brea.
Cheers to having me on your side.
[Chrishell] I love that.
I look forward
to taking you under my wing.
Uh! Cheers. That's so sweet. Thanks.
-That was surprisingly easy.
-That was like if a salad was a shot.
So what are your thoughts
on dinner the other night?
Well, it was nice to see everybody
outside of the office.
-Yeah, it always is.
-There were a few awkward moments.
So, you actually knew before I did
that Maya was pregnant.
I know... Honestly, though,
it was by accident.
I know it was an honest mistake,
but just be careful next time because
we're a really small group of people.
So secrets and things get out
and it causes explosions.
Okay. I have no defense.
-I know.
-I literally just still feel so bad.
Just live and learn.
But it seemed like Davina was
really calling you out.
It's frustrating that people are talking--
You did ask me about, like,
does he pay for stuff.
Yeah, and I think it's because
you don't really know. You know?
Okay.
You know what it is?
It was just interesting.
She kind of brought it up in conversation,
and so I asked her a few questions,
'cause I was trying to understand where
everybody's concern was coming from.
So I said,
"Well, is she paying for everything?"
And she was like, "I don't think so."
So I was like, "Okay."
But then, in front of Mary,
she was kind of like,
"Well, Chrishell said..."
and I was like, "I never said that."
First of all, I don't know them,
so I wouldn't say that.
When Davina threw me under the bus,
I'm not gonna be that person
that just doesn't say something.
So here's the thing
that I love about Davina,
is she's a lot like me. She's no bullshit.
Like, you know, she will say it how it is.
So she's one person
that you probably wanna be friends with.
If you don't own up
to the things that you say,
you're gonna get in trouble
in this brokerage. It's small.
So you need to not get your feelings hurt
and don't think that you're being
thrown under the bus
because you're being called out
on something that you've said.
She can't be meek
and she has to be stronger.
And if she's not, she's not gonna last.
As long as you know don't... with me...
I would say, don't... with Davina,
and be careful around Mary.
You'll do fine.
I know you have a tough exterior, but you
seem like a teddy bear on the inside.
I'm bound and determined to see it.
No. I'm a total teddy bear.
I can see it.
I was, like, the nerd in high school.
Everyone made fun of me.
Like everyone said
I would go nowhere in life.
-I swear to God I could cry right now.
-What?
No, I swear to God.
-No! I'm like, "Why am I crying?"
-No.
No, but, seriously, I am a teddy bear.
I really am.
I'm also, like,
very just to the point and honest,
and sometimes
that comes across, like, the wrong way.
And I hate that. That's not my intention,
'cause people don't have
a sense of humor.
What were you like in high school?
I'm curious.
I come from poverty.
So I was, like, the smelly kid,
'cause sometimes I didn't have
running water. Now, I'm not gonna cry.
Um... But, um, I really relate to you,
because it's one of those things
where it's like people
would never assume that now
'cause I've worked so hard
to get away from that.
It's crazy. Like, you really don't know
what people have been through,
and I think you're so strong. I really do.
But I'm just really happy
that you joined our brokerage,
-and that, um--
-You'll keep me in line.
If I give you a hard time, I'm sorry.
It's not my intention,
I just want you to be professional
and I want people to love you.
So, that's my only intention for you,
I promise.
-I feel a hug coming on.
-I feel a hug coming on!
Come here. Aw, that's so nice.
-Aw. I love--
-Thank you so much for inviting me out.
-[Christine] Of course.
-[Chrishell] It's been so nice.
[Christine] Of course.
♪ Ooh, on top of the world ♪
♪ On top of the world ♪
[Brandon] So they built
all the way up to the hillside.
As high as they could, yes.
And it doesn't look as tall
from down here,
but I swear it's insane.
So look at the view.
This is not even anything compared
to what else you're gonna see.
I'm looking at those power lines,
and I know you said--
Well, you won't be looking at them
for very long, 'cause they'll be dropped.
He's spending half a million dollars
to drop the powerlines.
[Heather]
It's around 20,000 square feet...
-Okay.
-...which is giant.
And this is actually
the last home of this size
that is allowed to be built in the Hills.
The city shut it down. So this is it.
So basically when you walk in, on this
side, there's a full gym, two saunas--
-Two saunas? Why would you need two?
-I mean, why wouldn't you?
Atrium with a palm tree.
-That sells it right there.
-Who has a palm tree in their home?
And there's a beautiful movie theater.
-This is all pool right?
-The pool, yeah.
The pool basically wraps
around the whole house,
so I think that you should get in
and take a little swim.
Oh, I can feel it already.
Are you sure you don't want to get in?
I've decided not to swim today.
You could have rafts in here
and float around like a lazy river.
-[Brandon] A giant swan!
-[Heather] There you go.
-How big is this?
-A hundred and fifty feet long.
Have you ever been
inside of a pool that big?
At a hotel, yes,
but on a private property, no.
Hello, this is a huge listing.
It'd be the biggest one I've ever had
and the biggest one
at the Oppenheim Group.
It would make a huge statement for me.
So tell your client this is
the last one of this size.
You better jump on it.
It's gonna go quick.
We can do a really good
housewarming party if he buys it.
-Or when. Let's say when he buys.
-Yes!
Let's do it.
♪ You've got to let it go ♪
♪ You've got to live out loud ♪
♪ You've got to let them know ♪
♪ We're flying up above the clouds... ♪
-Me so hungry.
-Oh, I know. Me too.
Oh, my God, I'm starving.
Yeah. Can't wait to get my coffee.
We haven't seen each other a lot.
-You've been really busy.
-I know.
-It's ridiculous.
-Your work, yeah.
I think we saw each other more
when we weren't living together.
[chuckles] Yeah.
[Mary chuckles] This is getting...
-[Romain] Yeah, you're working so much.
-Jeez. It's tough.
Good morning, welcome to Fig.
Hi, my name is Chris.
I'll be your server today.
-Thank you.
-Some menus for you.
All right. Thank you.
I think I'm gonna do
an egg white omelette with avocado.
[Chris] Perfect.
I'm going to get, like, a toast
with juice and coffee.
-[Chris] Sounds good.
-Cool. Thank you.
-How was your morning?
-It was good. Busy. Yeah.
You know that house
that I showed the other day...
-The one you really liked?
-...on Fremont? Yeah.
-I really want you to see it.
-Yeah?
It's so cool.
It feels homey...
and just hip at the same time.
Yeah? What did he say about it?
-Are they gonna make an offer?
-She likes it.
-She likes it a lot.
-[Chris] A latte for you, miss.
-[Mary] Thank you.
-[Chris] For you, sir, whole milk latte.
[Mary] Thank you.
We should probably start thinking about
what we're gonna do once we get married,
-like where we're gonna live.
-Mm-hmm.
Do we want to keep
the same kind of, like, condo...
-situation...
-I don't know.
...or do we want a house?
Because, after seeing that Fremont house,
I'm, like, that's what I want. [chuckles]
Um, I've thought about it.
I don't know if it would be better for us
to just keep living where we are.
Yeah.
But we need to have
a couple extra bedrooms,
for whenever Austin comes out to visit
-or whenever your parents come.
-Mm-hmm.
So we need at least two bedrooms,
maybe three so we can have an office.
[chuckles]
Do you want to get a bigger place?
Do you think it's important for us
to have more room, or do you just...
I don't know.
I also will see,
I have to do, you know, more...
-Maintenance and stuff on it. I know.
-Yeah. More, I guess.
I mean, it doesn't need to be huge, but--
No, that's for sure, I mean...
I don't know.
-I guess--
-What style do you like?
You know, with a hot tub.
-With a hot tub?
-Yeah.
What? [laughs]
A hot tub? Okay.
Or a pool or I don't know,
but something like that.
Well, I mean, you have to have a house,
it's cool, no?
Yeah.
If you're all set,
I'll have the check dropped.
-Perfect, thank you.
-My pleasure.
-Let me know if you need anything.
-[Romain] Thank you.
[gasps] I don't have my--
Do you have your wallet?
Give me your card.
I don't have my card with me, baby.
-It's in my car.
-Uh-huh. I see how you are.
[Romain chuckles]
-Babe, I swear I don't have it.
-Mm-hmm.
I really don't have my wallet.
Put a ring on the finger and now you're
like, "Baby, you can pay, right?"
I forgot my card. [laughs]
Yeah, right. I'm looking in there
when we get back.
-Yeah!
-I'm joking.
-This is cute.
-Yeah, this is super cute.
So, you know,
this area called, like, Hollywood Dell.
East Hollywood Hills,
like old, classic, Spanish.
Yeah, it's pretty cool,
they remodeled the whole property.
[Chrishell] I can't wait
to see inside. This is pretty.
-Yeah, super nice. Very Spanish.
-[Chrishell] I like all the greenery.
All right. Welcome
to our Spanish revival new listing.
It's not your typical,
like, open floor plan.
It's an amazing house.
So you kind of know the stats, right?
You have the setup sheet.
Why don't... I'm gonna be your client
and you're just gonna show me the house.
Oh, a little role play.
If I'm a buyer and I'm walking
into a Sunday open house
and I'm asking the agent questions,
they better know the answers.
Size, price, details.
So I wanted to test Chrishell
and play with her a little bit
just in case she will see the open house
on Sunday when I cannot be there.
So this is a beautiful Spanish home
and it's very unique.
Um, you know,
you won't find this everywhere.
A lot of the homes around here
are very modern.
But that's the thing.
When I sent you the listings that I want,
I wanted a modern house, so why
did you bring me to the Spanish one?
-Oh.
-So can we just leave?
-I'm kidding. I'm giving you a hard time.
-My God! [laughs]
I'm kidding, okay.
This is beautiful. All right.
Shit, you really got me. [laughs]
Okay. All right.
So, uh, as you see
this is a huge, nice living space
with a beautiful fireplace.
Yeah, I got eyes. I can see the fireplace.
We've got four bedrooms,
four bathrooms--
My phone is ringing. Hold on.
It's my husband.
-Oh, okay.
-Hello?
Yes, I'm seeing a house here,
just a second, bye.
I'm just... I'm giving you a hard time,
'cause this is what clients sometimes are.
-Okay, go ahead.
-Okay.
Ahem.
All right, I wanna see the kitchen.
Okay, I will move you into the kitchen.
This next, it is a gorgeous open space.
The kitchen runs beautifully
into the dining room.
Yeah, right? It's pretty.
And you've got an amazing fireplace,
which you never get.
You've got these balconies
outside the kitchen,
which could open it up,
have amazing ambiance.
And the really high ceilings
are incredible.
Is this chandelier gonna stay?
Is the seller gonna keep it?
If you want to keep the chandelier,
you would need to specify that
with your offer.
Good answer. Let me tell you.
People buy millions of dollars of house
and they argue about little things.
I'm like, "Come on, guys.
You can replace a chandelier."
-But, no, they want that specific one.
-That I knew.
-That was on my test.
-That's a good answer.
So let me give you a round of applause.
-Oh, thank you.
-You passed the audition.
You know, like, real estate is
such a great business
once it's up and going,
but, I mean, you know, my first year,
it took me one year to sell a house.
It was not even a house, it was a condo.
-Really?
-Yeah.
Like, you can say to Jason,
like, "Throw me some bone." Like--
[laughs] Sorry.
I just... It's so cute when you say that.
"Throw me some bone."
Not the real bone,
like, you know, real estate bone.
-A lead, a listing.
-[Chrishell chuckles]
Okay, so tell it nicely, like,
"Hey, Jason, I do want to be more
in the game,
I just don't want to deal with leases.
Would you co-list with me?" Yeah.
Yeah, I'll ask.
See if he can give it to you. Like,
one listing, one condo, one house.
He doesn't want to go to  the Valley.
He doesn't wanna go to the Valley
or East Hollywood Hills
and he's also not gonna cross the 405.
Jason? Where is Jason?
-I think if he gets-- [chuckles]
-He's not there.
-He could be.
-Jason is nowhere to be found.
-[Maya] Look how cute the balcony is, huh?
-Oh, this is so cute.
I think it'll sell for sure really quick.
Yeah, I hope so.
I really hope so, 'cause I flew
from Miami literally last night.
-Really?
-Yeah.
To... do the open houses
and do the showing.
You don't look like
you flew in last night.
-I know, you know. [chuckles]
-Maybe it's that glow you have going on.
I wish I could say it's the glow,
but it's just so early.
-I know.
-And the thing is, it's like,
you know, I had the miscarriage
and then the other miscarriage.
And then I had a cyst on my ovary.
-Oh, my God.
-Yeah.
-You got it taken off?
-I did.
-Okay.
-The gynecologist,
she couldn't separate them
and she had to remove the ovary,
so I'm 36 with one ovary now.
It's like, great.
I can't imagine being
under that much stress.
So if you ever need to decompress,
-I mean, I'm here.
-Thank you, girl. Thank you so much.
-I really appreciate that.
-Of course.
♪ Singing la, la, la, la, la, la ♪
♪ I'm moving on ♪
[phone ringing]
[dog whimpers]
Hello, this is Mary.
-Hi, Mary. It's Emily.
-Hey, Emily.
Listen, I wanted to talk to you.
I am in love with the house
and I want to put an offer in.
That's amazing.
Here's the thing
is I want to put in the best price
so that I don't lose this house.
I don't want to have to go back and forth.
So what do you think that price would be?
Four-seven-seven-five.
-That's kind of the sweet spot.
-You think that's the best we can do?
I think in this situation, it is.
Four-seven-seven-five
is where we would land
if we did go into negotiations,
so I think if we went ahead
and just came in strong,
we could win the deal.
Okay. I think that sounds good.
I wanna try
and lock this in today if we can,
-'cause that would be amazing.
-Perfect. Okay.
I'll let the agent know.
We'll send it over now.
-Awesome. Thank you so much, Mary.
-Okay.
♪ Don't stop ♪
♪ I'm living my best life
Living my best life ♪
♪ Do what I feel like ♪
♪ Living my best life ♪
♪ I'm staying up all night ♪
♪ Keeping it all right ♪
♪ Do what I feel like ♪
♪ Living my best life ♪
[Maya] I'd kill you if would tell me
not to bring tennis shoes.
Like, no way in hell
I'm wearing high heels.
-I got your back.
-I can't.
This is not Ferragamo-friendly terrain.
[Maya] No, not at all.
Nineteen thousand square feet lot?
-Eighteen-five.
-Wow.
Yeah. You've been mentioning to me
you want to learn more about development,
-so this is a great opportunity.
-Yeah, I want to be more involved
and be knowledgeable more about,
you know, the whole process.
So if you could just show me.
[Maya] I think learning
about real estate development
is very important,
because eventually I want to do it
or maybe invest with my client
and be part of the deal
versus just an agent who negotiates
between buyer and seller.
I want to have a piece of the pie, too.
On this project, I was really involved.
So I actually engaged
the architect and the builders.
I reviewed these plans for a month,
I would say,
to make sure everything was good to go.
In fact, we went as far as
to change the name of the street.
-It used to be Pinto Place.
-Yeah, Pinto, right?
I'm like, wait, that street had
a different name. It was Pinto Place.
Yeah, now it's Hummingbird Place.
Yeah, 'cause what was Pinto?
Like, what is that?
-It's more like a bean.
-Yeah. [chuckles]
The Bird Streets is an area in LA
in Hollywood.
It's right north of Sunset Plaza
up in the Hills,
and it's a very prestigious area.
You have so many celebrities
that live around that pocket
and not to mention
all the nice, brand new constructions.
The houses are going
for 30, 40, 50 million.
If you really want to be able
to step up the game
for house flippers and renovations
or for development,
-it's a whole different skill set.
-That's interesting, you know?
Like, my husband is in finance,
and obviously I'm in real estate.
Like, I kind of want to try to convince
him to start from, like, a small flip
and then just go from there.
-It makes sense.
-Just something that's crossed my mind.
What's up with you guys?
Everything's good?
Yeah. Actually, I'm pregnant.
Shut up.
-Really?
-Yeah, it's very early.
-Come here! Wow.
-Thank you.
Thank you,
but it's, honestly, it's very early.
Whatever happens, happens.
But because I already had
two miscarriages,
he's like, "Why don't you just
take it easy and stay more in Miami
and maybe just refer business
to the girls?"
Just so you know, I'm here.
I'm committed. I'm not going anywhere.
Just have to juggle everything, right?
I just want to be perfect
in every aspect in my life.
Being a good wife,
being a good real estate agent
to my clients,
and obviously being a good, perfect mom.
And I think you cannot have it perfect.
Something has to give at some point.
I just don't know what.
I can't be available for my clients
all the time once I have a newborn.
I'm proud of how
you've handled everything.
-Thank you.
-I can sympathize tremendously
-with what you're going through.
-Can you?
-Well, I can sympathize.
-You don't even have a dog.
I'm pregnant and I'm really... sweaty.
You can show me
the plans in the office where it's cool
and a glass of, like,
I would say champagne, but lemonade.
-I can't even offer you drinks anymore.
-I know. I'm lame.
I have hot flashes.
♪ And I feel it coming ♪
♪ And I know the reason to shine ♪
-Hi, Mary.
-Hey, Emily, they accepted your offer.
-That's awesome.
-Four-seven-seven-five
We're gonna open escrow today.
I'm heading to the office right now
and I will send you all the remaining
documents for you to sign.
I'm so happy, you have no idea.
I'll call you just in a little bit
when I get to the office.
-Sounds good.
-Okay, bye.
♪ These are walls that never break ♪
♪ Oh, oh ♪
♪ Nobody could take our place ♪
♪ Everybody wants to be us ♪
All right, we've got, actually,
a few things we need to go over here.
Let me get an update from everyone here.
Mary, you wanna give us a quick update?
I have some good news.
I just got the offer accepted,
and we are closing the deal
on the Fremont house.
[Maya] Congratulations.
We need, like, a bell. Every time
someone closes something, we ring a bell.
Uh, Christine, go ahead.
Um... Well, obviously I would love to get
my client Jacob up to the house after, um,
those finishes are put in.
I'd love him to see it
and get a better idea
of the direction that it's going in.
Um, and then I have a showing
for my $14 million house.
This is probably the sixth showing.
I hope it goes good.
Okay, good luck with that, Christine.
Chrishell?
Okay, so, uh... on the Tara Drive,
I'm gonna try to find a new buyer
and I'm gonna try and get
some backup offers.
We're still gonna sell it. I have faith.
♪ I know what I've got ♪
♪ I know what I need ♪
Hi, guys.
-[all] Hey.
-[Heather] What's up?
How are you? I'm so sorry I'm late.
I have some exciting news.
So I think I have a potential buyer
for the $40 million house.
-No way!
-Are you serious?
Christine, you heard that?
You heard that, Christine?
I heard it. I have someone
who's interested as well,
but, you know, let the games begin.
The race is on, girl.
I guess you're not moving to Sweden, huh?
Christine, don't tell me you bought her
the flight ticket already,
like, one-way back to Sweden.
Yeah, she gets miles, coach ticket.
-Oh, no, honey. Oh, no.
-Norwegian Airlines.
You're still together, though, and---
Yeah, we're still together.
Long distance is hard,
but we'll make it work.
[Jason] Oh, ten percent of the time,
it works every time.
How would you know?
Have you done it?
-[Davina] Taking advice from this guy!
-Don't listen to him.
♪ Get it, get it ♪
[Mary] Are you excited?
-Yes, I'm so happy.
-[chuckles] Good!
Oh, my God.
Welcome home.
I think you guys are going
to just love it here.
♪ And then we pop the hood
And, yeah, we love it... ♪
[Mary] This is it. You've got your keys.
-I know. Oh, my gosh.
-You've got your new house.
I cannot believe it.
And then here is a bottle of wine
to celebrate
It is one of the best feelings
when you finally get to hand over the keys
to your clients, because that is
such a huge day for them.
The house is yours.
It's so beautiful.
Thank you for everything.
Of course, I hope you're so happy here.
I am. This is my dream.
Good.
[Mary] But it's bittersweet because...
I would love to be handed my own set
of keys for a house like this one day.
♪ I ♪
♪ Recall ♪
♪ The times you dropped by... ♪
[Mary]
Do you feel like you're missing out?
Eh, a little bit.
♪ We'd stare into the sun ♪
♪ Run wild like dragonflies ♪
[Mary]
He doesn't want kids for ten years.
What?
[Chrishell] No, don't cry, Mary. Oh.
-[exhales]
-[Christine] Yeah, it's so sad.
[Mary] Do you want a house?
♪ I converse ♪
♪ I can't do this alone ♪
♪ Remember me ♪
♪ When I'm gone ♪
♪ In dreams ♪
♪ We're gonna live on ♪